Historic Image Collection HIC
Stage
Historic Image Collection
1800-1960
Stage
HIC
800 Linear feet
- 4th of July
  General
  See: Days, Special
- 4th of July
- Accidents
  See Also: Union Station
- Adams Morgan
  See: Residential Sections
- Advertising
- Aerial Views
  See: Views
- Agriculture, Department of
  See Also: Bridges - Agriculture, Department of; See Also: Houses - General (For Tree House Images)
- AIDS Quilt
- Air and Space Museum, National
  See: Museums - Air and Space
- Air Raid Shelters
  See: World War II - Civil Defense
- Airplanes
  See: Aviation; See: Airports
- Airports
- Airports - General
- Airports - Dulles Airport
- Airports - National Airport
- Airships
- Alexandria, Virginia
- Alleys
  See Also: Housing Alleys
- American Art, Museum of
  See: Patent Office
- American Association of University Women
  See: Societies, Clubs and Organizations
- American Federation of Labor
- American History Museum, National
  See: Museum - American History; See: Smithsonian Institution - American History
- American Legion Building
  See Also: Societies, Clubs and Organizations
- American Pharmaceutical Building
- American Red Cross
- Anacostia
- Anacostia Community Museum
  See: Museums: Anacostia Neighborhood
- Anacostia River (and Eastern Branch)
  See Also: Residential Sections - Anacostia
- Analostan Island
  See: Theodore Roosevelt Island
- Anderson Cottage
  See: Soldiers Home
- Apartment Houses
  Also See: Housing
- Apex Building
  See Also: Federal Trade Commission; See Also: Triangle
- Aqueducts
- Arboretum
  See Also: Parks; See Also: Trees, Flowers, Shrubs
- Archives, National
  See Also: Triangle
- Arlington, Virginia
- Arlington National Cemetery
- Arlington National Cemetery - General
- Arlington National Cemetery - Amphitheater
- Arlington National Cemetery - Arlington House
- Arlington National Cemetery - Civil War Unknown Tomb
- Arlington National Cemetery - Confederate Monument
- Arlington National Cemetery - L'Enfant Tomb
- Arlington National Cemetery - Maine Memorial
- Arlington National Cemetery - Memorials
- Arlington National Cemetery - Temple of Fame
- Arlington National Cemetery - Tomb of the Unknown
  See Also: Harding, Warren J.; See Also: Visitors; See Also: World War I
- Armistice Day
- Armory
- Army and Navy Club
- Army War College
- Arsenal
- Art Exhibits
- Art Galleries
  See Also: Museums - Hirshhorn
- Art Galleries - Corcoran
- Art Galleries - Freer
  See Also: Smithsonian Institution - Freer Gallery
- Art Galleries - National Gallery of Art
  See Also: Museums - National Gallery of Art
- Art Galleries - Phillips
- Arts and Industry Museum Building
  See: Smithsonian Institution - National Museum
- Associations
- Automobile
  See Also: Tidal Basin
- Aviation
- Aviation - General
- Aviation - Langley Aerodrome
- Aviation - Wright Brothers
- Banks
- Banks - American National
- Banks - Brightwood Savings
- Banks - Bank of Columbia
- Banks - Central National
- Banks - Citizens National
- Banks - Columbia National
- Banks - District National
- Banks - Farmers and Mechanics National
- Banks - Federal American National
- Banks - First Federal Savings and Loan
- Banks - Freedman's Savings
- Banks - Lincoln National
- Banks - National Bank of Washington
- Banks - National Metropolitan
- Banks - National Safe Deposit
- Banks - National Savings
- Banks - Riggs
- Banks - Second National
- Banks - Union Trust
- Banks - Washington Loan and Trust
- Banks - Washington Savings
- Bars
  See: Restaurants; See: Saloons
- Barges
  See: Canals - C And O Canal
- Barthodi Fountain
  See: Botanic Garden; See: Fountains
- Baseball
  See: Sports
- Basketball
- Bethesda Naval Center
  See: Hospitals - National Naval Medical Center
- Bicycles and Bicycling
- Big Brothers
- Black History Month
- Blacks
  See Also: Houses
- Bladensburg, Maryland
- Blimps
  See: Airships
- Board of Trade
  See: Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade
- Boats and Boating
  See Also: Potomac River - Boats and Boating; See Also: Ferries; See Also: Sports; See Also: Tidal Basin; See Also: Waterfront
- Bonus Army/Bonus March
  See: Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations
- Books and Book Sellers
- Botanic Garden
  See Also: Fountains
- Boundary Stones
- Boy Scouts
- Boys' Club
- Braddock's Rock
- Bridges
- Bridges - General
- Bridges - 9th Street
- Bridges - 11th Street
- Bridges - 14th Street (Rochambeau)
- Bridges - 16th Street
- Bridges - Agriculture, Department of
- Bridges - Anacostia
- Bridges - Aqueduct
- Bridges - Arlington Memorial
- Bridges - Benning Road
- Bridges - C And O Canal
- Bridges - Cabin John
- Bridges - Calvert Street
- Bridges - Capital Beltway
- Bridges - Chain Bridge
- Bridges - Dumbarton
- Bridges - East Capitol Street
- Bridges - Georgetown Bridge
- Bridges - H Street Bridge
- Bridges - Independence Avenue
- Bridges - K Street
- Bridges - Key, Francis Scott Bridge
- Bridges - Klingle Bridge
- Bridges - Long Bridge
- Bridges - M Street
- Bridges - Massachusetts Avenue
- Bridges - Monroe Street
- Bridges - New York Avenue
- Bridges - Park Road
- Bridges - Pedestrian
- Bridges - Pennsylvania Avenue
- Bridges - Piney Branch
- Bridges - Railroad
- Bridges - Reflecting Pool
- Bridges - Rochambeau
  See: Bridges - 14th Street
- Bridges - Rock Creek Park
- Bridges - Roosevelt, Theodore
- Bridges - Sousa, John Phillip
- Bridges - South Capitol Street
- Bridges - T Street
- Bridges - Taft, William Howard
- Bridges - Three Sisters Bridge
- Bridges - Tidal Basin
- Bridges - Tunnicliffe
- Bridges - Washington Channel
- Bridges - Wilson, Woodrow
- Bridges - Wisconsin Avenue
- Brightwood Race Track
  See: Horses
- Building Associations
- Buildings and Offices
- Buildings and Offices - General
- Buildings and Offices - Acacia Mutual
- Buildings and Offices - Albee
- Buildings and Offices - American Automobile Association
- Buildings and Offices - American Building
- Buildings and Offices - American Federation of Labor
- Buildings and Offices - Arlington Building
- Buildings and Offices - Arts Club
- Buildings and Offices - Atlantic Building
- Buildings and Offices - Bliss Building
- Buildings and Offices - Bond Building
- Buildings and Offices - Census, Bureau of
- Buildings and Offices - Chamber of Commerce
- Buildings and Offices - Coast Guard
- Buildings and Offices - Colorado Building
- Buildings and Offices - Commercial Bank
- Buildings and Offices - Cornwell, C.C. Building
- Buildings and Offices - Customs House
- Buildings and Offices - Davidson Building
- Buildings and Offices - Department of Education
- Buildings and Offices - Department of Energy
  See: Buildings - Forrestal Building
- Buildings and Offices - Dove Building
- Buildings and Offices - Equitable Building
- Buildings and Offices - Farragut Building
- Buildings and Offices - Federal Storage Company
- Buildings and Offices - Fendall Building
- Buildings and Offices - Firemen's Insurance Company
- Buildings and Offices - Forest Industries
- Buildings and Offices - Forrestal Building
- Buildings and Offices - Franklin Fire Insurance Company
- Buildings and Offices - Fulton
- Buildings and Offices - Glover Building
- Buildings and Offices - Government Heating Plant
- Buildings and Offices - Hoe Building
- Buildings and Offices - Home Builders
- Buildings and Offices - Homer Building
- Buildings and Offices - Insurance Building
- Buildings and Offices - International Club
- Buildings and Offices - Jordan Piano Company
- Buildings and Offices - Kellogg Building
- Buildings and Offices - Kiplinger Editors Building
- Buildings and Offices - Labor, Department of
- Buildings and Offices - Lafayette Building
- Buildings and Offices - Lemon Building
- Buildings and Offices - Liberty Loan Building
- Buildings and Offices - Lord Memorial Hall
- Buildings and Offices - Machinists Building
- Buildings and Offices - Maltry Building
- Buildings and Offices - Manhattan Coffee Mills
- Buildings and Offices - McShain Building
- Buildings and Offices - Methodist Building
- Buildings and Offices - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade
- Buildings and Offices - Mills Building
- Buildings and Offices - Montgomery Building
- Buildings and Offices - Moses Building
- Buildings and Offices - Munsey Building
- Buildings and Offices - National Defense Building
- Buildings and Offices - National Palace
- Buildings and Offices - National Press Club
- Buildings and Offices - Norris Building
- Buildings and Offices - Pennsylvania Building
- Buildings and Offices - People's Mutual Benefit Insurance Co.
- Buildings and Offices - Potomac Electric Power Company
- Buildings and Offices - Presidential Building
- Buildings and Offices - Real Estate Title Insurance Company
- Buildings and Offices - Reconstruction Finance Corporation
- Buildings and Offices - Riggs Building
- Buildings and Offices - Riggs Fire Insurance
- Buildings and Offices - Sanders and Stayman
- Buildings and Offices - Shoreham
- Buildings and Offices - Southern Railway
- Buildings and Offices - Standard Oil Company
- Buildings and Offices - Story and Cobb
- Buildings and Offices - Suffridge Building
- Buildings and Offices - Sun Building
- Buildings and Offices - Swartzell, Rheem and Hensey
- Buildings and Offices - Tower Building
- Buildings and Offices - Transportation
- Buildings and Offices - Union Building
- Buildings and Offices - Union Trust Company
- Buildings and Offices - United States News Annex
- Buildings and Offices - Walker Building
- Buildings and Offices - Walker-Johnson Building
- Buildings and Offices - Wardman Building
- Buildings and Offices - Washington Building
- Buildings and Offices - Washington Gas
- Buildings and Offices - Washington Loan and Trust Company
- Buildings and Offices - Washington Post Buildings
- Buildings and Offices - Wilkins Building
- Buildings and Offices - Winder Building
- Buildings and Offices - Woodward Building
- Buildings and Offices - World Center Building
- Buildings and Offices - Wyatt Building
- Building Museum
  See: Pension Office
- Bullets, Washington
- Bureau of Engraving and Printing
  See: Engraving and Printing, Bureau of
- Bureau of Standards
  See: Standards, Bureau of
- Burnes Cottage
  See: Houses - 17th Street
- Buses
  See: Transportation; See: Streets
- Business
- Buzzard's Point
- C and P Telephone
  See: Telephone
- Cabin John
- Canal Boats
- Canals
- Canals - Chesapeake and Ohio Canal
- Capitol, US
  See Also: Views; See Also: Fountains; See Also: Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue; See Also: Supreme Court; See Also: Tiber Creek; See Also: Transportation; See Also: Weather
- Capitol, US - Art and Sculpture
- Capitol, US - Exterior
- Capitol, US - Grounds
- Capitol, US - Interior
- Capitol, US - Statuary Hall
- Capitol Bicycle Club
  See: Sports - Bicycling
- Capitol Transit Company
  See: Street Railroads
- Capitol Plaza
  See: Fountains
- Car Barn
  See: Transportation
- Cars
  See: Automobiles; See: Transportation
- Carillons
- Carnegie Institution of Washington
- Cartoons - Political
- Cemeteries
  See Also: Arlington National Cemetery
- Cemeteries - General
- Cemeteries - Cedar Hill
- Cemeteries - Congressional
- Cemeteries - Fort Lincoln
- Cemeteries - Glenwood
- Cemeteries - Oak Hill
- Cemeteries - Rock Creek
- Cemeteries - Woodlawn
- Census Bureau
- Centennial Committee
- Center Market
  See: Markets; See: Street Vendors
- Chamber of Commerce, US
- Cherry Blossoms
  See: Trees - Cherry; See: Parades - Cherry Blossom; See: Tidal Basin
- Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company
- Children
- Children's Homes
- Chinatown
  See Also: Ethnic Groups; See Also: Residential Section; See Also: Restaurants
- Chinese New Year
  See: Ethnic Groups
- Christmas and Christmas Tree, National
  See: Biography - Hoover, Herbert; See: Days, Special
- Churches
- Churches - General
- Churches - 16th Street Universalist
- Churches - All Saints Episcopal
- Churches - All Souls Memorial Episcopal
- Churches - All Souls Unitarian
- Churches - Allen Becton Memorial
- Churches - AME Zion
- Churches - Anacostia Baptist
- Churches - Anacostia Methodist
- Churches - Annandale Methodist
- Churches - Annunciation Catholic, Church of the
- Churches - Asbury Methodist
- Churches - Ascension Episcopal
- Churches - Atonement Episcopal Diocesan Chapel
- Churches - Atonement Lutheran
- Churches - Augustana Lutheran
- Churches - Bethany Baptist
- Churches - Bethel Pentecostal Tabernacle
- Churches - Bible-Way
- Churches - Bradburn Memorial Methodist
- Churches - Bradbury Heights Methodist
- Churches - Bridge Street Presbyterian (Georgetown)
- Churches - Brookland Baptist
- Churches - Calvary Baptist
- Churches - Calvary Gospel
- Churches - Calvary Methodist
- Churches - Calvary Protestant
- Churches - Cathedral of St. Peter and St. Paul
  See: Washington National Cathedral
- Churches - Centennial Baptist
- Churches - Chapel of the Holy Spirit (Episcopal)
- Churches - Chapel of the Redeemer (Episcopal)
- Churches - Chevy Chase Baptist
- Churches - Chevy Chase Methodist
- Churches - Chinese Christian
- Churches - Christ Baptist
- Churches - Christ Church (Alexandria, VA)
- Churches - Christ Church (Georgetown)
- Churches - Christ Church (Washington)
- Churches - Christ Lutheran
- Churches - Christian Baptist
- Churches - Church of Christ
- Churches - Church of God
- Churches - Church of God in Christ
- Churches - Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints Mormon
- Churches - Church of Our Father
- Churches - Church of Our Savior Episcopal
- Churches - Church of the Brethren
- Churches - Church of the Covenant Episcopal
- Churches - Church of the Covenant Presbyterian
- Churches - Church of the Epiphany Episcopal
- Churches - Church of the Holy Communion Episcopal
- Churches - Church of the Incarnation Lutheran
- Churches - Church of the Nativity (Catholic)
- Churches - Church of the Pilgrim Presbyterian
- Churches - Church of the Reformation (Lutheran)
- Churches - Cleveland Park Congregational
- Churches - Columbia Heights Christian
- Churches - Concordia Lutheran
- Churches - Congress Heights Baptist
- Churches - Congress Heights Methodist
- Churches - Disciples of Christ
- Churches - Douglas Memorial Methodist
- Churches - Downtown Baptist (Alexandria, VA)
- Churches - Dumbarton Avenue Methodist
- Churches - Dutch Reformed
- Churches - E Street Baptist
- Churches - Eastern Presbyterian
- Churches - Eldbrooke Methodist
- Churches - Emmanuel Episcopal
- Churches - Emory Methodist
- Churches - Epworth Methodist
- Churches - Falls Episcopal
- Churches - Fifteenth Street Presbyterian
- Churches - Fifth Baptist
- Churches - First Baptist
- Churches - First Church of Christian Science
- Churches - First Church of the Nazarene
- Churches - First Congregational
- Churches - First Evangelical and Reformed
- Churches - First Methodist Meeting House
- Churches - First Presbyterian
- Churches - First Unitarian
- Churches - Foundry Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Fourth Church of Christ Scientist
- Churches - Full Gospel Tabernacle
- Churches - Galbraith A.M.E.Z.
- Churches - Garfield Christian Memorial
- Churches - Garoenia Spiritual Temple
- Churches - Georgetown Presbyterian
- Churches - Good Samaritan Community Church
- Churches - Gorsuch Methodist
- Churches - Gospel Mission
- Churches - Gospel Temple
- Churches - Grace Baptist
- Churches - Grace Episcopal
- Churches - Grace Evangelical Lutheran
- Churches - Greater New Hope Baptist
- Churches - Greek Church and Adventist Church
- Churches - H Street Christian
- Churches - Hamline Methodist
- Churches - Holy Comforter Catholic
- Churches - Holy Name Catholic
- Churches - Holy Rosary Catholic
- Churches - Holyland Spiritual Temple
- Churches - I Street Meeting House
- Churches - Immaculate Conception, Church of the (Catholic)
- Churches - Ingram Memorial Congregational
- Churches - Jehoush Holiness Spiritual
- Churches - Keller Memorial Lutheran
- Churches - Lewis Memorial Methodist
- Churches - Lincoln Memorial Congregational
- Churches - Lincoln Road Methodist
- Churches - Luther Place Memorial (Lutheran)
- Churches - Luther Rice Memorial Baptist
- Churches - Marvin Methodist
- Churches - McKendree Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Methodist Meeting House
- Churches - Metropolitan A.M.E.
- Churches - Metropolitan Baptist
- Churches - Metropolitan Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Minnesota Avenue Christian
- Churches - Most Blessed Sacrament, Shrine of the (Catholic)
- Churches - Mount Airy Baptist
- Churches - Mount Moriah Baptist
- Churches - Mount Pleasant Congregational
- Churches - Mount Pleasant Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Mount Rainier Methodist
- Churches - Mount Vernon Place Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - National Baptist Memorial
- Churches - National City Christian
- Churches - National Memorial Church of God
- Churches - National Memorial Presbyterian
- Churches - National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception, Basilica of the
- Churches - Nativity and Resurrection Episcopal
- Churches - New Bethel Baptist
- Churches - New Jerusalem
- Churches - New York Avenue Presbyterian
- Churches - North Carolina Avenue Methodist
- Churches - Northminster Presbyterian
- Churches - Our Lady of Victory Catholic, Church of
- Churches - Pentecostal Holiness
- Churches - Petworth Baptist
- Churches - Pickney Memorial Episcopal
- Churches - Plymouth Congregational
- Churches - Potomac Heights Community
- Churches - Resurrection Episcopal
- Churches - Review and Herald Memorial Seventh Day Adventist
- Churches - Rhode Island Avenue Methodist
- Churches - River Road United Presbyterian
- Churches - Rock Creek Baptist
- Churches - Ryland Methodist
- Churches - Sacred Heart, Shrine of the (Catholic)
- Churches - Saint Agnes Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Alban's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Aloysins' Catholic
- Churches - Saint Ann's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Anthony's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Augustine's Catholic
- Churches - Saint David's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Dominic's Catholic
- Churches - Saint John's Episcopal (Georgetown)
- Churches - Saint John's Episcopal (Lafayette Square)
- Churches - Saint John's Episcopal (Maryland)
- Churches - Saint Joseph's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Margaret's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Mark's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Mark's and Incarnation Lutheran
- Churches - Saint Martin's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Mary's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Mary's Colored Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Mary's Episcopal Chapel
- Churches - Saint Mary's Lutheran
- Churches - Saint Matthew's Cathedral (Catholic)
- Churches - Saint Mathew's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Matthew's Lutheran
- Churches - Saint Nicholas Russian Orthodox
- Churches - Saint Patrick's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Patrick's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Paul's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Paul's Episcopal (Rock Creek)
- Churches - Saint Paul's Episcopal (Washington)
- Churches - Saint Paul's Lutheran
- Churches - Saint Paul's Methodist
- Churches - Saint Peter's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Stephen's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Stephen's Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Teresa's Catholic
- Churches - Saint Thomas Episcopal
- Churches - Saint Vincent de Paul Catholic
- Churches - Second Colored Baptist
- Churches - Sligo Seventh Day Adventist
- Churches - Society of Friends Meeting House
- Churches - South Bethany Baptist
- Churches - Southern Baptist
- Churches - Takoma Lutheran
- Churches - Takoma Park Baptist
- Churches - Temple Baptist
- Churches - Temple Church of God in Christ
- Churches - Trinity Episcopal
- Churches - Trinity Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Trinity Spiritual
- Churches - Union Methodist
- Churches - United Brethren Memorial
- Churches - United House of Prayer
- Churches - Ursuline Sisters Catholic Chapel
- Churches - Washington National Cathedral
- Churches - Waugh Methodist
- Churches - Way Back to Pentecostal
- Churches - Wesley Methodist Episcopal
- Churches - Western Presbyterian
- Churches - Westmoreland Circle Congregational
- Churches - Wilson Memorial Methodist
- Churches - Woodbridge Pilgrim
- Churches - Zion Evangelical Lutheran
- Churches - Circles and Squares
  See Also: Houses; See Also: Streets
- Circles and Squares - 12th Street Circle
- Circles and Squares - Dupont Circle
  See Also: Fountains; See Also: Subways
- Circles and Squares - Farragut Square
  See Also: Subways
- Circles and Squares - Franklin Square
- Circles and Squares - Grant Circle
- Circles and Squares - Iowa Circle
- Circles and Squares - Judiciary Square
  See: Subways
- Circles and Squares - Lafayette Square
  See Also: Memorials; See Also: White House
- Circles and Squares - Logan Circle
- Circles and Squares - McPherson Square
- Circles and Squares - Pershing Square
- Circles and Squares - Scott Circle
- Circles and Squares - Sheridan Circle
- Circles and Squares - Sherman Square
- Circles and Squares - Thomas Circle
- Circles and Squares - Ward Circle
- Circles and Squares - Washington Circle
- Circles and Squares - Union Square
- City Hall (Superior Court of DC)
  See Also: Courthouse and Courts; See Also: Hospitals
- City Planning
- Civil Defense
  See Also: World War II - Civil Defense
- Civil Rights
  See: Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations; See: Parades - Civil Rights
- Civil Service Commission
- Civil War
  See Also: Ferries; See Also: Forts; See Also: Parades - Civil War
- Clean-Up Campaign
- Clothing
- Colleges and Universities
- Colleges and Universities - American University
- Colleges and Universities - Benjamin Franklin University
- Colleges and Universities - Catholic University
- Colleges and Universities - Chevy Chase College
- Colleges and Universities - College of Preachers
- Colleges and Universities - Columbian University
- Colleges and Universities - District of Columbia Teacher's College
- Colleges and Universities - Dumbarton College of the Holy Cross
- Colleges and Universities - Gallaudet College
- Colleges and Universities - George Washington University
- Colleges and Universities - Georgetown University
- Colleges and Universities - Howard University
- Colleges and Universities - Trinity College
- Colleges and Universities - Washington Missionary College
- Colleges and Universities - Wayland Seminary
- Colleges and Universities - Wesley Theological Seminary
- Columbia Heights
  See: Residential Sections; See: Subways
- Commerce Department
- Congress
- Constitution Hall
- Continental Hall
- Contests
- Corcoran House
  See: Houses - Corcoran House
- Corrections, Department of
- Cosmos Club
- Courthouse / Courts
  See Also: City Hall; See Also: Hospitals
- Custis-Lee Mansion
  See: Arlington National Cemetery
- Dams
  See: Canals - C And O Canal; See: Potomac River
- Daughters of the American Revolution (DAR)
  See: Constitution Hall; See: Continental Hall; See: Societies, Clubs and Organizations
- Days, Special
- DC Bar Association
- Demonstrations
- Depots
  See: Railroads
- Description
- District Building
  See Also: City Hall
- Drug Stores
  See: Stores
- Dumbarton Oaks
  See: Museums - Dumbarton Oaks; See: Visitors
- Dumbarton Oaks Conference
  See: Visitors
- Eastern Market
  See: Markets
- Eisenhower Executive Office Building
  See: State, War and Navy Building; See: War Department
- Elections
- Electric Chair
- Electricity
- Embassies
- Embassies - Austro-Hungary
- Embassies - Bolivia
- Embassies - British - See: Great Britain
- Embassies - Brazil
- Embassies - Canada
- Embassies - Chile
- Embassies - China
- Embassies - Columbia
- Embassies - Cuba
- Embassies - Czechoslovakia
- Embassies - Dominican Republic
- Embassies - Finland
- Embassies - France
- Embassies - Germany
- Embassies - Great Britain
- Embassies - Guatemala
- Embassies - Haiti
- Embassies - Honduras
- Embassies - India
- Embassies - Indonesia
- Embassies - Israel
- Embassies - Italy
- Embassies - Japan
- Embassies - Liberia
- Embassies - Norway
- Embassies - Pakistan
- Embassies - Panama
- Embassies - Peru
- Embassies - Russia
- Embassies - Soviet Union - See: Russia
- Embassies - Venezuela
- Embassies - Yugoslavia
- Engraving and Printing, Bureau of